NYS PERB Agreements 5140
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Boards of Education: Comsewogue through Copake-Taconic Hills (Box 56)
  - Connetquot, 1972-1987 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Comsewoglie, 1989-2003 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Comsewoglie, 1976-1989 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Comsewoque, 1980-1985 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Copenhagen, 1974-1985 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: Copenhagen through Corinth (Box 57)
  - Copenhagen, 1970-2007 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Copenhagen, 1994-1996 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Copenhagen, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Copenhagen, 1986-1989 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Copiague, 1970-1997 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Copiague, 1969-1999 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Copiague, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Copiague, 1997-2004 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Copiague, 1977-1999 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Corfu-East Pembroke, 1969-1973 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Corfu-East Pembroke, 1970-1971 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Corfu-East Pembroke, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Corinth, 1968-2008 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Corinth through Cornwall (Box 58)
  - Corinth, 1968-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Corinth, 1988-2001 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Corinth, 1973-1974 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Corinth, 1998-2000 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Corning-Painted Post, 1971-2007 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Corning-Painted Post, 1969-1975 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Corning-Painted Post, 1968-1984 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Corning, 1992-2002 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Corning, 1970-1983 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Corning, 1968-1992 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Corning-Painted Post, 1983-2004 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Cornwall, 1987-2001 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Cornwall, 1974-2003 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Cornwall, 1970-1987 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Cornwall, 1970-2000 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Cornwall, 1982-1998 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Cortland through Coxsackie-Athens (Box 59)
  - Cortland, 1969-1975 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Cortland, 1995-2003 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Cortland, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Cortland, 1970-1995 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Cortland, 1980-1987 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Cortland, 1968-1997 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Cottage School, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Coxsackie-Athens, 1968-2005 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Coxsackie, 1995-2000 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Coxsackie-Athens, 1968-1992 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: Coxsackie-Athens through Cuba (Box 60)
  - Coxsackie-Athens, 1973-1994 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Coxsackie-Athens, 1973-2009 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Coxsackie-Athens, 1968-1993 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Croton-Harmon Schools, 1992-1997 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Croton, 1973-1979 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Croton Teachers Association, Inc., 1968-1998 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Croton-Harmon, 1970-1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Croton-Harmon, 1970-1992 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Croton-Harmon, 1968-1995 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Crown Point, 1986-1996 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Crown Point, 1992-2000 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Crown Point, 1971-2006 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Crown Point, 1968-1991 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Crown Point, 1985-1996 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Cuba, 1968-1994 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Cuba, 1969-1982 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Cuba, 1987-1995 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Cuba, 1985-2001 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Cuba, 1994-1996 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Cuba, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Cuba, 1994-2004 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Boards of Education: Dalton through Delhi (Box 61)
  - Dalton, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Dansville, 1968-1970 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Dansville, 1970-1979 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Dansville, 1994-1996 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Dansville, 1969-1984 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Dannemora, 1980-1988 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Deer Park, 1968-1976 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Deer Park, 1993-2002 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Deer Park, 1972-1983 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Deer Park, 1976-1998 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Deer Park, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Delaware Academy and Central School, 1970-1985 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Delaware Valley, 1972-1979 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Delaware, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Delaware, 1972-1986 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Delaware Valley, 1968-1977 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Delaware Valley, 1987-1994 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Delaware Valley, 2000-2002 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Delhi, 1975-1991 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Boards of Education: Depew through Dobbs Ferry (Box 62)
  - Depew, 1987-1997 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Depew, 1970-1983 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Depew, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Depew, 1969-1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Deposit, 1970-1992 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Deposit, 1968-1997 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Deposit, 1989-1993 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - DeRuyter, 1970-1974 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - DeRuyter, 2001-2005 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - DeRuyter, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - DeRuyter, 1978-2002 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Dobbs Ferry, 1969-1991 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Dobbs Ferry, 1968-1998 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Dobbs Ferry, 1969-1979 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Dobbs Ferry, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Dobbs Ferry, 1990-1999 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Dolgeville through Draper (Box 63)
  - Dolgeville, 1981-1992 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Dolgeville, 1968-1981 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Dolgeville, 1968-1992 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Dolgeville, 1992-2002 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Dover UFSD, 1995-2002 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Dover, 1968-1992 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Dover Union FSD, 1975-1979 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Dover, 1968-1996 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Dover - Educational Aides, Assistants, and Associates, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Downsville, 1997-2001 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Downsville, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Downsville, 1985-1994 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Draper, 1967-1978 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Draper, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Draper, 1968-1976 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: Dryden through Dunkirk (Box 64)
  - Dryden C.S., 1992-1999 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Dryden, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Dryden, 1968-1975 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Dryden, 1971-1992 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Dryden, 1969-1994 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Duanesburg, 1983-1991 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Duanesburg, 1986-2000 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Duanesburg, 1977-1983 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Duanesburg, 1968-1983 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Dundee, 1968-1993 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Dundee, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Dundee, 1993-2003 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Dundee, 1968-1974 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Dundee, 1974-2008 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Dunkirk, 1968-1974 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Dunkirk, 1974-1985 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Dunkirk, 1993-1999 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Dunkirk, 1968-1991 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Boards of Education: Dunkirk through East Greenbush (Box 65)
  - Dunkirk, 1974-1993 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Dunkirk, 1968-1996 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Durham, 1968-1970 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Durham, 1971-1974 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - East Aurora, 1968-2003 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - East Aurora, 1974-1998 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - East Aurora, 1973-1983 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - East Aurora, 1995-2006 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - East Bloomfield, 1991-1999 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - East Bloomfield - Profession Education Association, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - East Bloomfield, 1995-2003 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - East Greenbush, 1970-1998 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - East Greenbush, 1995-2002 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: East Greenbush through East Irondequoit (Box 66)
  - East Greenbush, 1978-2001 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - East Greenbush, 1974-1985 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - East Greenbush, 1968-1995 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - East Hampton, 1968-1997 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - East Hampton, 1982-2004 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - East Hampton, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - East Irondequoit, 1968-1995 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - East Irondequoit, 1969-1992 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - East Irondequoit, 1969-1998 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - East Irondequoit, 1991-1996 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - East Irondequoit, 1973-2003 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: East Islip through East Meadow (Box 67)
  - East Islip, 1972-1983 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - East Islip, 1991-1995 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - East Islip, 1973-1989 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - East Islip, 1968-1975 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - East Islip, 1968-1970 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - East Islip, 1976-2001 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - East Meadow, 1970-1982 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - East Meadow, 1974-1999 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - East Meadow, 1968-1989 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - East Meadow, 1968-1984 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - East Meadow, 1984-1993 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - East Meadow, 1988-1996 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - East Meadow, 1968-1983 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: East Moriches through East Rochester (Box 68)
  - East Moriches, 1970-1997 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - East Moriches, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - East Moriches, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - East Moriches, 1987-2002 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - East Quoque, 1972-1993 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - East Quoque, 1993-1998 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - East Quoque, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - East Ramapo, 1975-1981 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - East Ramapo, 1976-1990 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - East Ramapo, 1977-2001 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - East Ramapo, 1989-1995 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - East Ramapo, 1976-1984 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - East Rochester, 1968-1991 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - East Rochester, 1989-2000 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - East Rochester, 1968-1984 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: East Rockaway through East Syracuse (Box 69)
  - East Rockaway, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - East Rockaway, 1970-1981 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - East Rockaway, 1997-2002 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - East Rockaway, 1970-1994 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - East Rockaway, 1975-1997 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - East Syracuse-Minoa, 1978-2001 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - East Syracuse-Minoa, 1976-1996 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - East Syracuse, 1995-2005 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - East Syracuse-Minoa, 1974-1984 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - East Syracuse-Minoa, 1969-2001 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: East Syracuse through Eastport (Box 70)
  - East Syracuse, 1984-2002 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - East Williston, 1976-1985 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - East Williston, 1989-2001 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - East Williston, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - East Williston, 1978-1994 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Eastchester, 1987-1994 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Eastchester, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Eastchester, 1975-1981 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Eastchester, 1969-1973 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Eastchester, 1968-1988 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Eastchester, 1975-1991 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Eastport, 1975-1992 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Boards of Education: Eastport through Edwards (Box 71)
  - Eastport, 1970-1980 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Eastport, 1991-1995 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Eastport, 1970-1991 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Eden, 1975-1988 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Eden, 1976-1983 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Eden, 1991-1999 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Eden, 1988-1993 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Eden, 1971-1978 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Edgemont, 1983-1995 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Edgemont, 1986-2004 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Edgemont, 1994-1998 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Edinburg, 1981-2000 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Edinburg, 1987-1995 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Edinburg, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Edmeston, 1993-1999 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Edwards, 1970-1979 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Edwards, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Boards of Education: Edwards through Ellenville (Box 72)
  - Edward-Knox, 1986-1996 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Elba, 1972-1989 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Elba, 1990-1995 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Elba, 1983-1998 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Elba, 1986-1994 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Elba, 1980-1995 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Eldred, 1994-2001 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Eldred, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Eldred, 1986-1992 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Elizabethtown-Lewis, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Elizabethtown-Lewis Central School, 1970-2000 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Ellenburg, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Ellenville, 1968-1988 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Ellenville, 1972-1984 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Ellenville, 1969-1983 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Ellenville, 1972-1998 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Ellicotville through Elmire Heights (Box 73)
  - Ellicottville, 1997-2000 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Ellicottville, 1994-1997 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Ellicottville, 1988-1990 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Elmira, 1984-2002 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Elmira, 1991-2001 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Elmira, 1979-2005 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Elmira, 1991-2002 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Elmira Heights, 1969-1984 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Elmira Heights, 1991-2002 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Elmira Heights, 1990-1999 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Elmira Heights, 1974-1999 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Elmont through Elwood (Box 74)
  - Elmont, 1976-1994 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Elmont, 1984-1991 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Elmont, 1969-1971 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Elmont, 1975-2006 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Elmont, 1983-1991 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Elmsford, 1978-1988 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Elmsford, 1987-1999 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Elmsford, 1968-1973 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Elmsford, 1990-1997 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Elwood, 1970-1984 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: Elwood through Fairport (Box 75)
  - Elwood, 1990-2002 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Elwood, 1969-1983 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Elwood, 1969-1996 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Endicott, 1981-1983 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Endicott, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Evans-Brant, 1980-2000 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Fabius, 1972-1977 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Fabius, 1996-2005 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Fabius-Pompey, 1972-1982 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Fabius, 1978-1992 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Fabius, 1970-1991 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Fabius-Pompey, 1987-1993 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Fabius-Pompey, 1980-2002 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Fairport, 1985-1998 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Fairport through Falconer (Box 76)
  - Fairport, 1971-1981 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Fairport, 1998-2006 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Fairport, 1975-1995 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Fairport, 1980-2002 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Falconer, 1971-1984 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Falconer, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Falconer, 1992-1995 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Falconer, 1969-1988 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Falconer, 1988-1998 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: Fallsburgh through Fayetteville-Manlius (Box 77)
  - Fallsburgh, 1974-1991 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Fallsburgh, 1981-1997 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Fallsburgh, 1991-2002 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Fallsburgh, 1973-1974 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Fallsburgh, 1968-1978 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Farmingdale, 1968-1978 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Farmingdale, 1988-1995 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Farmingdale, 1968-1979 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Farmingdale, 1980-1991 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Fayetteville-Manlius, 1971-1986 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Fayetteville-Manlius, 1989-1997 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Fayetteville-Manlius through Floral Park (Box 78)
  - Fayetteville-Manlius, 1970-1989 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Fayetteville-Manlius, 1986-2000 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Fayetteville-Manlius, 1994-2003 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Fayetteville-Manlius, 1980-2005 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Fillmore, 1989-1997 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Fillmore, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Fillmore, 1988-1994 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Floral Park Bellerose, 1971-1986 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Floral Park Bellerose, 1986-2001 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Floral Park Bellerose, 1984-2004 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Floral Park Bellerose, 1987-2002 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Florida through Fort Ann (Box 79)
  - Florida Union, 1976-1996 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Florida Union, 1998-2001 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Florida UFSD, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Florida, 1984-2001 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Fonda-Fultonville, 1976-1987 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Fonda Fultonville C.S., 1992-1995 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Fonda-Fultonville CSD, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Fonda-Fultonville, 1987-1994 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Forestville, 1974-1988 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Forestville, 1972-1998 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Forestville C.S., 1994-2004 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Forestville, 1987-1995 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Forest Ann, 1970-1993 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Fort Ann School District, 1993-1998 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Fort Ann - Teachers, 1981-1984 (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: Fort Edward through Franklin (Box 80)
  - Fort Edward, 1985-2002 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Fort Edwards, 1975-1988 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Fort Edward, 1988-2003 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Fort Plain, 1970-1984 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Fort Plain, 2000-2004 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Fort Washington, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Frankfort-Schuyler, 1990-1997 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Frankfort-Schuyler, 1968-1974 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Franklin, 1970-1993 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: Franklin through Fredonia (Box 81)
  - Franklin, 1974-1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Franklin, 1993-2001 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Franklin, 1985-1993 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Franklin Square, 1977-1991 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Franklin Square, 1971-2008 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Franklin Square, 1993-2008 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Franklin Square, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Franklin Square, 1988-1997 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Franklinville, 1971-1983 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Franklinville, 1991-2008 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Franklinville, 1972-2008 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Franklinville, 1970-1983 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Franklinville, 1991-1999 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Fredonia, 1968-2002 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Fredonia through Frewsburg (Box 82)
  - Fredonia, 1988-1999 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Freeport, 1970-1983 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Freeport, 1969-1992 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Freeport, 1971-1984 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Freeport, 1971-2004 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Freeport, 1990-1996 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Frewsburg, 1972-1983 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Frewsburg, 1972-2002 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Frewsburg, 1970-1984 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Frewsburg, 1972-2002 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: Friendship through Fulton (Box 83)
  - Friendship, 1994-1997 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Friendship, 1972-1985 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Friendship, 1971-1987 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Friendship, 1969-1994 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Friendship, 1970-1999 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Frontier, 1969-1993 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Frontier, 1970-2003 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Fulmont, 1971-1982 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Fulmont, 1991-2003 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: Fulton through Galway (Box 84)
  - Fulton, 1969-1994 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Fulton, 1970-1977 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Fulton, 1968-2000 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Fulton, 1980-1994 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Galway, 1968-1993 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Boards of Education: Galway through Gates-Chili (Box 85)
  - Galway, 1972-1979 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Galway, 1987-1994 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Galway, 1969-2004 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Gananda, 1971-1988 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Gananda, 1988-1994 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Garden City, 1975-1977 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Garden City, 1991-2000 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Garrison, 2001-2004 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Garrison, 1973-2001 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Garrison, 1987-1997 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Garrison, 1969-1990 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Garden City, 1976-1988 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Garden City, 1970-1995 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Garden City, 1989-1997 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Gates-Chili CSD, 1979-2005 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Gates Chili, 1968-1990 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Gates through Geneva (Box 86)
  - Gates Chili, 1971-1997 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - General Brown, 1971-2005 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - General Brown, 1972-1984 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - General Brown, 1971-1998 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - General Brown, 1968-2002 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Genesee Valley, 1996-2000 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Genesee Valley CSD, 2000-2003 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Genesee, 1970-2008 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Geneseo C.S., 1992-2002 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Geneseo, 1982-1997 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Geneva, 1970-1987 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Geneva, 1971-1981 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Geneva, 1992-2000 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Geneva through Gilboa-Conesville (Box 87)
  - Geneva, 1973-1984 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Geneva, 1970-1986 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - George Junior, 1987-2006 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - George Washington, 1973-1990 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Germantown, 1996-2000 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Germantown, 1974-1985 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Germantown, 1975-1994 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Gilbertsville, 1997-2000 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Gilbertsville, 1970-1997 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Gilboa-Conesville, 1971-1999 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Gilboa-Conesville CSD, 1977-1981 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Gilboa-Conesville, 1990-1996 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Gilboa-Conesville, 1968-1988 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Gilboa-Conesville, 1968-2002 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Glen Cove through Glens Falls (Box 88)
  - Glen Cove, 1990-1997 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Glen Cove, 1968-1991 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Glen Cove, 1970-1994 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Glens Falls, 1980-1987 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Glens Falls, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Glens Falls, 1993-2002 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Glens Falls, 1970-1996 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Boards of Education: Glens Falls through Gouverner (Box 89)
  - Glens Falls, 1993-1997 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Gloversville, 1969-2001 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Gloversville, 1994-2001 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Gloversville, 1971-2009 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Gloversville, 1988-2000 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Gorham, 1968-1969 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Goshen, 1971-1985 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Goshen, 1980-1995 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Goshen, 1972-1980 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Goshen, 1992-2003 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Goshen, 1969-1996 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Gouverneur, 1979-2005 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Boards of Education: Gouverner through Granville (Box 90)
  - Gouverneur, 1989-2002 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Gouverneur, 1974-1982 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Gouverneur, 1996-1999 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Gouverneur, 1971-1996 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Gowanda, 1976-1996 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Gowanda, 1989-2002 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Gowanda, 1971-1982 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Gowanda, 1987-2002 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Graham, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Graham, 1986-1991 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Grand Gorge, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Grand Island, 1971-1981 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Grand Island, 1990-1993 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Granville, 1990-2003 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Granville, 1972-1988 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Granville, 1972-1985 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Granville through Greater Amsterdam (Box 91)
  - Granville, 1970-2000 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Grand Gorge, 1971-1981 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Grand Gorge, 1968-1980 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Grand Island, 1969-1992 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Grand Island, 1971-1990 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Grand Island, 1985-1996 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Graham, 1969-1986 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Graham School, 1971-1973 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Great Neck, 1993-2004 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Great Neck, 1968-1979 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Great Neck, 1993-2000 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Greater Amsterdam, 1970-1985 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Greater Amsterdam, 1994-2001 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Greater Amsterdam through Great Neck (Box 92)
  - Greater Amsterdam, 1970-1976 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Greater Amsterdam, 1977-1990 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Greater Amsterdam, 1968-1990 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Greater Amsterdam, 1968-1998 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Greater Johnstown, 1971-1987 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Greater Johnstown, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Greater Johnstown, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Greater Johnstown, 1984-1997 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Great Neck, 1968-1987 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Great Neck, 1971-1993 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: Great Neck through Greenburgh (Box 93)
  - Great Neck, 1984-2008 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Greece, 1968-1990 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Greece, 1985-2004 (Box 93, Folder 3)